AHMD BABIKER ALMAHI

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

+971-563179971

• ahd.bkr19999@gmail.com

• Al Ain, UAE

— PERSONAL DETAILS—

Date of birth: 24 / 03 / 1999 - Visa status: UAE Resident Visa - Nationality: Sudanese

-PROFILE SUMMARY---

I am a Proficient "Full Stack Developer" with nearly five years experience of working.

I have worked in many institutions in Sudan and the UAE.

And I have extensive experience in my field of work which increases my experience and skills.

I have many great skills and experiences specific to my fields of work.

and I am ready to offer all my effort and use my skills and experience for the benefit of your esteemed institution.

I also have many practical and personal skills that I hope will benefit your esteemed institution.

I can work organized, broadly and accurately with excellent leadership.

SKILLS AND STRENGTHS-

- · UI/UX Design.
- Front-End Development.
- Web Development.
- HTML5 &CSS3 & JavaScript.
- Problem-Solving. Critical
- Thinking.
- · High communication skills. Team
- Collaboration & leadership.

- · Code Review.
- Problem solving skills.
- Organizational Skills. Performance
- Optimization.

2/2023 - 11/2023

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Bloom Tech Company. - "Remotely Work"

(Dubai, UAE)

"Front-End Developer"

- Collaborating with designers and back-end developers to translate design concepts into functional and responsive web applications.
- Developing clean, reusable, and well-documented front-end code using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.
- Implementing responsive design principles to ensure optimal user experience across all devices (desktop, mobile, tablet). Optimizing
- website performance for speed and efficiency.
- Testing and debugging code to ensure flawless functionality across different browsers. Staying up-to-
- date on the latest front-end development trends and technologies.
- Learning and growing your skillset to contribute to the company's technological advancements. Contributing to a
- collaborative and supportive development environment

Khartoum Bank.	
(khartoum,Sudan)	

"Data Entry Clerk"

- Entering customer data, account information, and financial transactions accurately and efficiently into the bank's computer system.
- Verifying the accuracy and completeness of all data entered to ensure data integrity. Maintaining and
- organizing electronic databases to ensure easy access to information. Resolving data entry errors and
- discrepancies promptly and efficiently.
 Following established data entry procedures and adhering to strict data security protocols. Supporting other departments with data-related tasks as needed.

Speed Flash Tech Company. (khartoum,Sudan)	10/2020 - 3/2021
"Full Stack Developer"	
Designing and developing user-friendly and visually appealing web applications from the ground maintaining scalable and secure back-end systems to power web applications. Integrating front-end and back-end components to ensure smooth functionality. Testing and debugging code to identify and resolve issues. Collaborating with designers, project managers, and other developers to deliver high-quality ap on the latest web development technologies and implementing them in projects.	
Zone Tech Company. (khartoum,Sudan)	12/2019 - 4/2020
"Back-End Ddeveloper Using Django framework"	
Developing and maintaining high-quality, secure, and scalable back-end applications using the implementing efficient and maintainable database structures. Writing clean, well-documented, and testable code. Collaborating with front-end developers and other team members to ensure seamless integration. Testing and debugging back-end functionality to identify and resolve issues. Deploying and monitoring applications in production environments to ensure smooth operation.	n of all application components.
Remotely Work.	3/2019 - 10/2019
"Front-End Developer"	
Collaborating with designers, back-end developers, and product managers to translate UI/UX deed code. Developing user interfaces (UIs) that are visually appealing, intuitive, and user-friendly. Implementing responsive design principles to ensure websites and applications function flawles maintainable, and well-documented code using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript frameworks like R Testing and debugging code to ensure optimal performance and a seamless user experience. Staying up-to-date on the latest front-end development trends and technologies to continuously	ssly across all devices. Writing clean, leact or Angular.
EDUCATION	

CERTIFICATIONS

LANGUAGES -

• English "Excellent"

• Bachelor of Software Engineering. - University of Alneelain, khartoum / Sudan - 2022

Django Framework - Elsafy Hegazy web education center / Khartoum, Sudan. System
 Analysis Using UML Diagrams - Senad Academy / Khartoum, Sudan. Software

• Front-End Course - Elzero web school (Online).

• Testing Course - Nezam Academy (Online).

• Arabic "Native"